[
    {
        "front": "ひく",
        "back": "引 \nto pull, to play",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "いんりょく",
        "back": "引力 \ngravity",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひきだし",
        "back": "引き出し \ndrawer",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "あける",
        "back": "開ける \nto open",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいてん",
        "back": "開店 \nopening a shop",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひらく",
        "back": "開く \nto open (file, book etc.)",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しめる",
        "back": "閉める \nto close",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "へいてん",
        "back": "閉店 \nclosing of a shop",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "とじる",
        "back": "閉じる \nto close (book or eyes)",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "へいかいしき",
        "back": "閉会式 \nclosing ceremony (IPL, Olympics)",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "さる",
        "back": "去 \nto leave",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょねん",
        "back": "去年 \nlast year",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "かこ",
        "back": "過去 \npast",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうきょ",
        "back": "消去 \nerasing",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しぬ",
        "back": "死ぬ \nto die",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ししゃ",
        "back": "死者 \ndead person",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうし",
        "back": "急死 \nunxpected, sudden death",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "びょうし",
        "back": "病死 \ndie due to disease",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "あつめる",
        "back": "集める \nto collect",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうごう",
        "back": "集合 \nto gather",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "あつまる",
        "back": "集まる \nto gather, assemble",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しる",
        "back": "知る \nto know",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "つうち",
        "back": "通知 \nnotice",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちしき",
        "back": "知識 \nknowledge",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しりあい",
        "back": "知り合い \nacquaintance or someone you know",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "うる",
        "back": "売る \nto sell",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばいてん",
        "back": "売店 \nselling counter / stall",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "うりば",
        "back": "売り場 \ndepartment counter",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "じどうはんばいき",
        "back": "自動販売機 \nvending machine",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "せつめい",
        "back": "説明 \nexplanation",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しようせつ",
        "back": "小説 \nnovel",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しようせつか",
        "back": "小説家 \nnovelist, writer",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもう",
        "back": "思う \nto think",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "しこう",
        "back": "思考 \nthoughts",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもいだす",
        "back": "思い出す \nremember, recollect",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    },
    {
        "front": "おもいで",
        "back": "思い出 \nmemory",
        "chapter": "N4 K20"
    }
]